<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rock The Universe</string>
    <string name="home_content">This is the Rock The Universe 2018 app. You can use this app to view the what bands are playing, at what time, and where. This app is not supported by Universal. </string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">splashScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_friday_night">FridayNight</string>
    <string name="title_activity_band_page">BandPage</string>

    <string name="title_activity_social_media">SocialMedia</string>
    <string name="title_activity_timeline">TimelineActivity</string>

    <string name="fTBlock1">•NA-NA</string>
    <string name="fTBlock2">•NA-NA</string>
    <string name="fTBlock3">•NA-NA</string>
    <string name="fTBlock4">•NA-NA</string>

    <string name="sTBlock1">•NA-NA</string>
    <string name="sTBlock2">•NA-NA</string>
    <string name="sTBlock3">•NA-NA</string>
    <string name="sTBlock4">•NA-NA</string>

    <string name="ld_name">Lauren Daigle</string>
    <string name="zw_name">Zach Williams</string>
    <string name="jc_name">Jesus Culture</string>
    <string name="red_name">RED</string>
    <string name="tm_name">TobyMac</string>
    <string name="tl_name">Trip Lee</string>

    <string name="rs_name">Ryan Stevenson</string>
    <string name="ff5_name">Family Force 5</string>
    <string name="bh_name">Brandon Heath</string>
    <string name="kc_name">for King and Country</string>
    <string name="cc_name">Casting Crowns</string>
    <string name="am_name">Andy Mineo</string>

    <string name="ld_info">•X:XX\n•Music Plaza</string>
    <string name="zw_info">•X:XX\n•Hollywood</string>
    <string name="jc_info">•X:XX\n•Music Plaza</string>
    <string name="red_info">•X:XX\n•Hollywood</string>
    <string name="tm_info">•X:XX\n•Music Plaza</string>
    <string name="tl_info">•X:XX\n•Hollywood</string>

    <string name="rs_info">•X:XX\n•Hollywood</string>
    <string name="ff5_info">•X:XX\n•Music Plaza</string>
    <string name="bh_info">•9:15\n•Hollywood</string>
    <string name="kc_info">•10:15\n•Music Plaza</string>
    <string name="cc_info">•7:30\n•Music Plaza</string>
    <string name="am_info">•6:00\n•Hollywood</string>

    <string name="ld_description">
      Lauren Ashley Daigle (born September 9, 1991) is an American contemporary Christian music singer-songwriter from Lafayette, Louisiana. Daigle is signed to the Centricity Music label. Her first full-length album, How Can It Be, was released in April 2015 and went on to achieve Platinum Record status. Daigle was awarded the New Artist of the Year title at the 2015 GMA Dove Awards, with her single "How Can It Be" winning the Song of the Year. The next year, she went on to win Dove Awards for Artist of the Year, Songwriter of the Year, and Best Contemporary Recorded Song of the Year, with her single "Trust in You." Daigle's album How Can It Be was nominated for a 2016 Grammy Award for Best Contemporary Christian Music Album; her single "Trust in You" was nominated for a 2017 Grammy Award for Best Contemporary Christian Music Performance/Song.
    </string>
    <string name="zw_description">
      Zachary Stephen Williams is a Grammy-award winning American Christian rock artist from Jonesboro, Arkansas. From 2007-2012 he was a member of Zach Williams & The Reformation (acoustic guitar, harmonica and vocals). He was also the lead singer of the Christian groups Brothers of Grace, and Zach Williams and the Brothers of Grace.
    </string>
    <string name="jc_description">
      Jesus Culture is an American international Christian revivalist youth outreach ministry that was formed at the Bethel Church of Redding, California. Jesus Culture Ministry hosts conferences and operates a record label, Jesus Culture Music, to share its message and spread worship. In 2013, Jesus Culture moved to plant a church in Sacramento. Meetings started on September 14, 2014.
    </string>
    <string name="red_description">
      Red (also stylized R3D or RED) is an American rock band from Nashville, Tennessee, formed in 2002 by brothers guitarist Anthony Armstrong and bassist Randy Armstrong, with lead vocalist Michael Barnes. The band's first lineup also consisted of drummer Andrew Hendrix and guitarist Jasen Rauch. Since 2014, the band's line-up has consisted of the core trio of the Armstrongs and Barnes with touring drummer Dan Johnson.
    </string>
    <string name="tm_description">
      Toby McKeehan (born Kevin Michael McKeehan; October 22, 1964), better known by his stage name TobyMac (styled tobyMac or TOBYMAC), is a Christian hip hop recording artist, music producer, songwriter and author.\n
      He has charted 20 solo singles on Billboard's Christian Songs list. He was first known for being a member of the Christian vocal trio DC Talk, staying with them from 1987 until they went on hiatus in 2001. He has since continued a successful solo career with the release of six studio albums: Momentum (2001), Welcome to Diverse City (2004), Portable Sounds (2007), Tonight (2010), Eye on It (2012), This Is Not a Test (2015), as well as two remixed albums of the first two albums titled Re:Mix Momentum and Renovating Diverse City respectively, and one remix album for albums number three and four titled Dubbed and Freq'd: A Remix Project (2012). He now has a fourth remix album titled "Eye'm All Mixed Up". He also has a full-length Christmas album Christmas in Diverse City (2011), which was his first holiday album. He became only the third Christian artist to have a No. 1 debut on Billboard 200 chart with Eye on It.
    </string>
    <string name="tl_description">
William Lee Barefield III (born December 17, 1987), better known by his stage name Trip Lee, is an American rapper, singer, poet, and author. Signed to Reach Records, he has recorded both as a solo artist and as a founding member of the 116 Clique. Originally from Dallas, Texas, he now resides in Atlanta, Georgia, and is a teaching pastor at Cornerstone Church. He first gained recognition after appearing on the Reach Records website at the age of 16. His third album, Between Two Worlds, was nominated for two Dove Awards and won the Stellar Award for Best Hip Hop Album in 2011.
    </string>

    <string name="rs_description">
Ryan Dale Stevenson (born January 21, 1979) is an American Christian musician and guitarist, who primarily plays a contemporary Christian music and worship style of music. His sponsor is Gotee Records, owned by Christian music artist TobyMac. He released three extended plays, Yesterday, Today, Forever, with BEC Recordings, Champion of the World, independently, and Hold Nothing Back, with Gotee Records. His first studio album, Fresh Start, was released on September 18, 2015, with Gotee Records. He's had five songs chart on the Billboard charts, "Holding Nothing Back", "The Human Side", "Not Forgotten", "All Yours" and "Eye of the Storm".
    </string>
    <string name="ff5_description">
      FF5 (formerly known as Family Force 5, The Phamily, Ground Noise and The Brothers) is an American Christian rock band from Atlanta, Georgia. The band formed in 2005 by brothers Solomon "Soul Glow Activatur", Joshua "Fatty", and Jacob "Crouton" Olds along with their two friends, Nathan Currin "Nadaddy" and Brad Allen "20 Cent" later replaced by Derek Mount "Chapstique". The group has released five studio albums, nine EPs, and two remix albums. They are often noted for their raucous, party-centric personae and eclectic mix of genres, ranging from rap metal to dance-pop.\n
      In 2018, the remaining two members, Jacob and Joshua Olds, re-branded the group as FF5 and released their EP, El Compadre, on March 2, 2018.
    </string>
    <string name="bh_description">
Brandon Heath Knell (born July 21, 1978) better known by the stage name Brandon Heath, is a contemporary Christian musician from Nashville, Tennessee. He has released six studio albums: Don't Get Comfortable (2006), What If We (2008), Leaving Eden (2011), Blue Mountain (2012), No Turning Back (2015), and Faith Hope Love Repeat (2017). He is best known for the No. 1 "I'm Not Who I Was" and "Give Me Your Eyes". He was nominated four times at the Dove Awards of 2008 and won in the "New Artist of the Year" category. His second album was nominated for "Gospel Album of the Year" at the 51st Grammy Awards of 2009.
    </string>
    <string name="kc_description">
      For King and Country, stylized as for KING and COUNTRY and formerly known as Joel and Luke as well as Austoville, is a Christian pop duo composed of Australian brothers Joel (born 5 June 1984) and Luke Smallbone (born 22 October 1986). The Nashville-based brothers' 2012 debut record Crave has received praise, and the brothers were declared by Billboard as one of the "New Artists To Watch" for 2012. American Songwriter described them as "Australia's answer to Coldplay."\n
      SUSIE Magazine raves, "It takes only one listen to the brothers' rich, upbeat, alternative sounds and thoughtful lyrics to understand their sudden popularity."
    </string>
    <string name="cc_description">
Casting Crowns is a contemporary Christian and Christian rock band started in 1999 by youth pastor Mark Hall, who serves as the band's lead vocalist, as part of a youth group at First Baptist Church in Downtown Daytona Beach, Florida. They later moved to Stockbridge, Georgia, and more members joined. Some members of the band currently work as ministers for Eagle's Landing First Baptist Church in McDonough, Georgia. The band has won a Grammy and a Dove Award.
    </string>
    <string name="am_description">
Andrew Mineo (born April 17, 1988), is an American hip hop artist, producer, and video director from New York City. He is signed to Reach Records and his creative initiative Miner League. In addition to his solo work, he is a member of Reach Records' hip hop collective 116 Clique.
    </string>

    <string name="sr1_name">Sarah Reeves</string>
    <string name="sr2_name">Sarah Reeves</string>
    <string name="db1_name">Dan Bremnes</string>
    <string name="db2_name">Dan Bremnes</string>
    <string name="1k_name">1K Phew</string>
    <string name="bon_name">Bonray</string>
    <string name="ac_name">Aaron Cole</string>
    <string name="rc_name">Riley Clemmons</string>

    <string name="sr1_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>
    <string name="sr2_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>
    <string name="db1_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>
    <string name="db2_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>
    <string name="1k_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>
    <string name="bon_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>
    <string name="ac_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>
    <string name="rc_info">•X:XX\n•Fan Zone</string>

    <string name="sr1_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="sr2_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="db1_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="db2_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="1k_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="bon_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="ac_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="rc_description">This band will be playing at the fan zone sponsored by Coca-Cola</string>

</resources>
